她赢得干脆
但对面这位科尔涅娃
也不是任人拿捏的资格赛新秀
北京时间8月10日凌晨3点31分
多伦多国家银行公开赛女单1/8决
赛
首盘她一路带走5局
把比分拉到5比1
科尔涅娃没有轻易服软
连救两个破发点
把这一盘硬拖到3比5
次盘她彻底占据主动
一路把比分拉开
6比1锁定这场比赛
I thought I served really well.
我觉得今天发球发得挺好
She's a great returner, puts a lot of balls back.
她接发球太好了，总能把球放回场里
So I had to mix it up, not rely too much on power.
所以我得多变化球路，不能太依赖力量
I think her demeanor — she didn't get too negative out there.
我最欣赏她的心态——场上没怎么显出低落
She's obviously a great talent, had success in the juniors.
她显然是个好苗子，青少年时期就很成功
I'm sure we'll have many more matches in the future.
以后我们肯定还有更多交手的机会
I do it for the love of the game, tennis is my first love.
我是因为热爱才打球，网球永远是我的初恋
I love my family too, one of the top things in my life.
我也爱我的家人，这是我生命里最重要的事之一
Reaching the quarterfinal here, I think, is the most fun.
能打进这里的八强，我觉得才是最开心的事
她说 以后肯定还有更多交手的机会
那会是什么时候？